<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CMI Open Day</string>
    <string name="opendaybutton">more information</string>
    <string name="de_scroller_werkt_lol" translatable="false">de scroller werkt lol</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Test" translatable="false">CMI Open Day, 04–4–2019\n12:00 – 16:00\nInformatica, Technische Informatica, Communicatie</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Test2" translatable="false">CMI Open Day, 04–6–2019\n17:00 – 20:00\nInformatica, Communicatie</string>
    <string name="open_days">Open Days</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Informatica" translatable="false">H.04.208/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 107</string>
    <string name="Technische_Informatica" translatable="false">Technische informatica</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Technische_Informatica" translatable="false">H.03.108/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 107</string>
    <string name="CMGT" translatable="false">CMGT</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_CMGT" translatable="false">WD.05.018/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 103</string>
    <string name="Communicatiewetenschappen">Communication</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Communicatiewetenschappen" translatable="false">WN.01.014/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 99</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="shareString">Share using what?</string>
    <string name="shareBody1">On</string>
    <string name="shareBody2">, I am going to an open day at the CMI of the Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences! Learn more at https://www.hogeschoolrotterdam.nl/</string>
    <string name="calendarMessage">Opening calendar...</string>
    <string name="calendarTitle">CMI Open Day</string>
    <string name="calendarBody">CMI Open Day of</string>


    <string-array name="studyCourseBody">
        <item>We make a software engineer out of you. You\'re going to be working on the development of software for many different applications. You will be able to analyse, design and implement complex IT systems.\n\nSoftware is all around us. You are the specialist in creating large and complex software information systems that work fast, safe and efficiently. For example, think about developing a functional app, but also about analyzing large amounts of data from social media. While developing these systems, you will come into contact with many different programming languages. In the first year, you\'ll learn to program in Python and the more advanced programming languages Java and C#. From the second year on, you will decide for yourself what programming language(s) you want to use. In addition to programming and developing software, you will also learn to cooperate in a team.\n\nAfter completing the Software Engineering course, you will be equipped with knowledge and abilities for a wide range of careers within the area. From positions like data engineer, software developer and software engineer, you will be able to keep growing in IT indefinitely.\n\nAre you interested in the latest technological developments? Are you curious, a little quirky, and someone who follows through? The Software Engineering course may be what you\'re looking for!\n\nTHE FIRST YEAR\n\nIn the first year, you will be orienting yourself within the field of Software Engineering. Every education period consists of 10 weeks in which you are taught concepts and skills from the field. There\'s a course Development, where you learn to program, and the course Analysis, where you learn to solve problems before you start programming. There will also be paid attention each period to the development of communicative skills, and you will work in a group of students on two projects, each lasting half a year.\n\nAFTER THE FIRST YEAR\n\nAfter mostly getting to know aspects of the professional field, in the main phase you will be diving deep into these aspects, both theoretically and practically. Together with students from other courses, you will be working on innovative projects which involve real companies from Rotterdam.\n\nIn the project, you will be working on simulated environments with your group, and you will apply your theoretic knowledge. You will work toward an end solution/product through increasing complexity, by using project development methods. In the third year you will be partaking in a twenty-week internship. In the second half of the third year and the first half of the fourth year, you will be taking self-chosen minors, after which you will go for graduation.</item>

        <item>Do you have a keen eye and ear on the stories behind brands and people? Are you creative with text and image, and fascinated by the world of media? Then the Communication course may be what you\'re looking for!\n\nOrganisations face major challenges. Promoting a new product, working with clients, employees and inhabitants, showing that you\'re doing good things for society. How do you manage, in this time of critical journalism, vlogging, societal discussions and rapidly changing trends?\n\nIn four years, our Communication course will turn you into a, what we proudly call, smart connector. A professional that can create smart connections. Using for example social tools, storytelling, big data and co-creation. You will be developing creative concepts such as media campaigns, events and story platforms. Based on good research, theory and strategy, and of course your own surprising ideas.\n\nFrom year 1 you\'ll be working with clients from the real world. From entrepreneurs from Rotterdam, start-ups and bureaus to national organizations. We work with innovative methods. You\'ll be working with the Scrum method, in which you flexibly and intensively work with the client. No class, course or project is the same. We will change the work type to what you learn: webinars, TED Talks, content cafés, meet-ups, guest lessons and company visits.\n\nTHE FIRST YEAR\n\nIn the first year, the focus will be on the practical aspects right away; everything you learn, you will apply in practical problem-solving. You will go on a company safari in Rotterdam and you will take a look in the kitchen of communication professionals. That way, you learn what communication is, and what you can do with it. What makes brands become successful? How does mediapsychology work? What role can you play within companies as a smart communicator? In small teams, you will work on projects, like developing an online magazine. In an editors board, you will work on developing interesting and interactive content (text ánd image), tending to a target audience. At the end of year one, you will research a subject from the communication course that you find interesting, and will write a thesis about it. Guerrillamarketing, storytelling, reputation management: what do you want to be an expert in?\n\nAFTER THE FIRST YEAR\n\nContext, concept and content: from year two on, the three Cs will be the main focus of the study course.\n\nContext\n\nWithin context, you will study the internal and external environments of organisations. What trends are relevant, who have an influence within and outside of the organisation? After all, making smart connections is all about being curious and understanding companies, stakeholders and societal developments. You\'ll develop your online and offline research skills and with all those insights you\'ll learn to create a communication strategy.\n\nConcept\n\nWith concept, your creativity is unleashed. This is where you create big ideas: creative concepts that make an organisation irresistible for its target audience. You will develop a sense for innovative solutions: what can we do with developments like Internet of Things and social sensing?\n\nContent\n\nLast but not least, you will learn to turn a concept into content: stories in text and image, a sharp media approach, and unforgettable events. In year three and four, you will develop a sense of strategy and will specialise further during your internship, a minor, and as a grand finale, your graduation assignment.</item>

        <item>At our school, studying often looks different. As a designer, you will not spend as much time in classrooms in the traditional way. We work together in the studio, for real clients.\n\nYou will design meaningful interactive products and services for the human being: from websites, apps, interactive setups, to full-on experience. Before you start designing, you will do elaborate research into the needs of the users and the environment in which your interactive design will be implemented. You will continuously check in with the client for whom you are designing, and you will also visit them on location. After all, designing is: making prototypes, testing, failing, redesigning, testing, adjusting, et cetera. You\'ll be busy sketching, researching and building on location. You will learn how to work around the needs and experience of the users and the clients. A pro-active attitude is a prerequisite for the designing process in Communication and Multimedia Design, as well as a healthy dose of curiosity, guts, and independence to deliver high quality work. We also expect you to be able to have a critical look at your own work, and act accordingly.\n\nThe first-year students now focus on elderly people that in some way experience physical or mental health problems and need caregiving. The client is seeking smart, new technological applications that will allow elderly people to live at home with the help of caregivers.\n\nThe CMD course challenges you to use your knowledge, creativity and talents for design for interactive products and services, that will improve the lives and environments of the people that use them.\n\nTHE FIRST YEAR\n\nThe first year consists of the following parts:\n\nIntroduction week\n\nDuring the introduction week, you will meet your fellow students, teachers and the study course. You will form your project team yourself with which you will work on the first Design Challenge in the studio.\n\nDesign Challenge\n\nThe year is divided into four quarters, in which you will work on a different realistic problem in a Design Challenge in your own studio, for a real product owner, with your project team.\n\nDesign Theory\n\nYou will also follow Design Theory. In this course, theory is the focal point. Some of this theory may not necessarily be used in your studio work. This deep background information helps you to put the Design Challenge and the designing field into perspective. Design Theory consists of lectures and seminars. What is being discussed in the lectures, you will work with in the seminars. Design Theory requires a high amount of self-study.\n\nPortfolio\n\nAs a CMD student, you are a starting professional and you will develop a portfolio in which you profile yourself as a designer, by using examples of your work. With a selection of your work (showcases), you will present yourself to the outside world: first your direct environment in the first year, but later, when you are applying for an internship for example, to design agencies and product owners.\n\nPersonal Challenge\n\nThe Personal Challenge is THE way of getting as much out of your education as possible, by having a personal challenge or fascination. You will be doing something that is relevant for you specifically, in your development as a designer. There will be four Personal Challenges in the first year.\n\nTools for design\n\nWithin the first Personal Challenge, you will follow the course \'Tools for Design\', in which you will develop various software-skills that will be used in the various Design Challenges.\n\nAFTER THE FIRST YEAR\n\nThe second through fourth years will consist of the following parts:\n\nDesign Challenge and labs\n\nThe second year of CND is all about going deeper. The projects become complexer and executed in semesters. During the Design Challenge, you will not only work in the studio, but you will be visiting labs each week where you will work individually on your personal development as a CMDer, guided by field experts. The labs complement the themes of the Design Challenge. Examples of labs are: User research &amp; Testing Lab, Visual Design Lab, Interaction Design Lab, Creative Concepting Lab, Creative Technologies Lab.\n\nDesign Theory\n\nYou will also follow Design Theory.\n\nPortfolio\n\nYou will also continue to showcase yourself using examples of your work in your portfolio.</item>

        <item>As a computer engineer, you work on modern IT systems that integrate hardware and software alike. Thanks to your knowledge in programming and hardware, you can work right where they overlap.\n\nIn our everyday lives, we have become increasingly dependent on IT systems. Traveling using public transport is only possible through OV Chipcard, your luggage at Schiphol ends up in the right location automatically, energy gauges become \'smart\' and medical procedures are sometimes performed by devices, and not by a surgeon. These are all examples where hard- and software come together to form a single system.\n\nAs a computer engineer, you will contribute to developing, securing, and maintaning these systems. During the course, you will learn the technical aspects of IT. You will learn to program in various languages, including the so-called \'lower-level\' languages for hardware applications. Using this, you will learn to develop solutions for various devices, robots and other modern systems. You are an all-rounder on all disciplines, but you also specialise in one or more aspects of the workfield. Think for example Machine Learning, Augmented Reality, Automated Systems and, of course, the IoT (Internet of Things), closely tied to Embedded Systems.\n\nTHE FIRST YEAR\n\nIn the first year, you will be orienting yourself within the field, and the base will be laid out for the rest of the course. During the first six months of the course, extra attention will be paid to bringing your math, physics, Dutch and English up to speed. Knowledge that will play an important role in your education. Also, programming, computer- and network systems will be a central point of attention in the first year. You will also apply the theoretical knowledge in practical assignments and projects.\n\nAFTER THE FIRST YEAR\n\nAfter your exploration in the first year, we will go deeper into your knowledge in the second year. You\'ll follow courses such as Computer Graphics, Sensor Technology and many more programming and technical courses to practice your work. In the third year, you will bring your knowledge and skills into the real world on your six-month internship, after which six months of projects will follow, with which you can specialise yourself. And finally, you will be profiling yourself in the fourth year where you will follow a minor in the first half, after which you will end the course with a practical thesis that, if possible, connects to your interests and plans for the future.</item>

        <item>Creative technologists invent and develop innovative digital products, with which the user is the main focus.\n\nAs CMGTer, you are a developer of interactive digital products: you develop web- and mobile apps and you know the basis of game development. The boundaries between these digital products and the physical world continue to fade ever faster. Therefore you will not be educated as a specialist in one specific programming language or platform, but as a flexible programmer that can teach themselves the possibilities of a new language or platform (smartphone, game console, Internet of Things) quickly and efficiently, with the goal of creating and developing interactive solutions for clients, that cross the borders of platforms and programming langages, in mind.\n\nA CMGTer from Rotterdam sets themselves apart from other programmers through sheer creativity, design-focused approach, and the knowledge and sense for the interaction between devices and people. With everything you create, the person you create it for is the focus of your thought process. That is why you will need a researching attitude, and you\'d want to get to know your users and involve them in the creation process of your product as much as possible. The work and possibilities of this creative technologist are heavily subject to change because of the continuous developments in the area. Now, the focus in the course is on web- and mobile technologies. Game technologies form a smaller part.\n\nCMGT-students will work together with students from the Communication and Multimedia Design course at times. This collaboration is important because working together with other creative specialists like designers and strategists when developing interactive solutions, leads to a higher quality end product.\n\nAfter the course, CMGTers will work as programmers at internet bureaus or other bureaus in the creative sector (advertising, marketing, design, innovation). A part will start their own business, or will work as a freelancer. Web Developer and Mobile Developer are also by far the careers that many graduates follow after completing the course.\n\nTHE FIRST YEAR\n\nYou will follow three subjects each quarter year: Designing, Programming and Media- and Technical Philosophy. The knowledge you acquire, you will apply directly in an intensive project named Contextual Learning Environment, which has a different theme every quarter year: internet of things, web, mobile and game.\n\nWithin the projects, you will develop ideas and experiment with techniques. When something doesn\'t work out, you do it differently the next time. A certain amount of self-management is needed for this to work well. Lessons will be provided according to what is needed at the time. You will reflect on your own development and will be guided by a coach.\n\nAFTER THE FIRST YEAR\n\nIn the second year, you will go deeper into your programming skills (like full-stack web &amp; mobile development) and you will go through projects with a high standard for technical and designing aspects. You must also be able to solve more complex problems. You will choose your own viewpoint; that way you will broaden your knowledge and skill as an undertaking, researching, designing or involved technologist.\n\nAfter your internship in the third year, the emphasis will be on your personal development even more. What are the technologies or points of interest that you would like to develop in further? In your fourth year, you will pick a minor in which you can broaden or deepen your knowledge. In the final semester you will graduate by executing a practically aimed research for an external assignee.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="studyCourseHeader">
        <item>Software Engineering</item>
        <item>Communication</item>
        <item>Communication and\nMultimedia Design</item>
        <item>Computer\nEngineering</item>
        <item>Creative Media and\nGame Technologies</item>

    </string-array>

    <!--ABOUT CMI PAGE-->
    <string name="aboutcmi_location" translatable="false">Wijnhaven 99–103–107</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_phoneNumber">Phone number: 010 – 794 4000</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_email" translatable="false">Email: CMI-Balie@hr.nl</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_website" translatable="false">Url: Hogeschoolrotterdam.nl</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_questionForm">QUESTION FORM</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_textHeader" translatable="false">Hogeschool Rotterdam (CMI)</string>

    <string name="aboutcmi_floorplan">FLOORPLAN</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_courses">COURSES</string>

    <!--FLOORPLAN PAGE-->
    <string name="floorplan_location" translatable="false">Wijnhaven 99-103-107</string>
    <string name="floorplan_floor_header">Floor</string>
    <string name="floorplan_building_header">Building</string>


    <string name="floorplan_up" translatable="false">+</string>
    <string name="floorplan_down" translatable="false">-</string>
    <string name="questionform_name">Name</string>
    <string name="questionform_subject">Subject</string>
    <string name="questionform_email" translatable="false">E-mail</string>
    <string name="questionform_message">Message</string>

    <string name="questionform_send">SEND</string>
    <string name="questionform_fill_in">Fill in</string>
    <string name="questionform_chooseApp">Choose an app for sending your message.</string>
    <string name="Communication_and_Multimedia_Design" translatable="false">Communication and Multimedia Design</string>
    <string name="Creative_Media_and_Game_Technologies" translatable="false">Creative Media and Game Technologies</string>
    <string name="Informatica" translatable="false">Informatica</string>
    <string name="software_engineering">Software Engineering</string>
    <string name="computer_engineering">Computer Engineering</string>

    <!--POPUPS-->
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="classroom">Classroom</string>
    <string name="_17_00_20_00_nwijnhaven_107" translatable="false">17:00 – 20:00\nWijnhaven 107</string>
    <string-array name="firstTimeArray">
        <item>12:30</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>17:00</item>
        <item>17:00</item>
        <item>17:00</item>
        <item>17:00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="secondTimeArray">
        <item>14:00</item>
        <item>14:00</item>
        <item>14:45</item>
        <item>14:00</item>
        <item>18:00</item>
        <item>18:00</item>
        <item>18:00</item>
        <item>18:00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="thirdTimeArray">
        <item>16:30</item>
        <item>16:45</item>
        <item>16:30</item>
        <item>16:00</item>
        <item>19:00</item>
        <item>19:00</item>
        <item>19:00</item>
        <item>19:00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="aboutcmi_content">The School of Communication, Media and Information Technology (CMI) provides higher education and applied research for the creative industry. As a committed partner CMI creates knowledge, skills and expertise for the ongoing development of the industry.\n\nCMI has five undergraduate programmes\n\nSoftware engineering\nComputer engineering\nCreative Media and Game Technologies\nCommunication &amp; Multimedia Design\nCommunication\nEach bachelor programme focuses on adding meaningful values to daily life by the use of communication, media or information technology. Students are being challenged to develop their competences such as creativity, entrepreneurship and interdisciplinary collaboration.\n\nOur education is practice driven and can be found throughout all years of our courses: practical cases and issues as a group assignment, embedded in education modules or advanced minors and electives, individual internships and graduate studies, but also in the form of guest lectures, workshops and business safaris (i.e. a trip where students visit multiple companies from an exploratory perspective).\n\nWe are constantly looking for themes in which cooperation with companies and universities is possible. The fresh view and up-to-date knowledge of our students often leads to innovative concepts, advanced insights and prototypes that are highly useful.\n\nCMI is closely linked to research group Creating 010, that conducts applied research to better utilize the potential of the creative industry in Rotterdam.</string>
    <string name="schoolname">Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences</string>
    <string name="homescreen">Home</string>
    <string name="courses">Courses</string>
    <string name="about_cmi">About CMI</string>
    <string name="ask_a_question">Ask A Question</string>
    <string name="floorplan">Floorplan</string>
    <string name="Communicatie">Communication</string>
</resources>
