<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CMI Open Day</string>
    <string name="opendaybutton">more information</string>
    <string name="de_scroller_werkt_lol">de scroller werkt lol</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Test">CMI Open Day, 04–4–2019\n12:00 – 16:00\nInformatica, Technische Informatica, Communicatie</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Test2">CMI Open Day, 04–6–2019\n17:00 – 20:00\nInformatica, Communicatie</string>
    <string name="open_days">Open Days</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Informatica">H.04.208/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 107</string>
    <string name="Technische_Informatica">Technische informatica</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Technische_Informatica">H.03.108/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 107</string>
    <string name="CMGT">CMGT</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_CMGT">WD.05.018/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 103</string>
    <string name="Communicatiewetenschappen">Communicatiewetenschappen</string>
    <string name="OpenDay_Communicatiewetenschappen">WN.01.014/ 12:00 – 16:00\nWijnhaven 99</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>


    <string-array name="studyCourseBody">
        <item>We make a software engineer out of you. You\'re going to be working on the development of software for many different applications. You will be able to analyse, design and implement complex IT systems.\n\nSoftware is all around us. You are the specialist in creating large and complex software information systems that work fast, safe and efficiently. For example, think about developing a functional app, but also about analyzing large amounts of data from social media. While developing these systems, you will come into contact with many different programming languages. In the first year, you\'ll learn to program in Python and the more advanced programming languages Java and C#. From the second year on, you will decide for yourself what programming language(s) you want to use. In addition to programming and developing software, you will also learn to cooperate in a team.\n\nAfter completing the Software Engineering course, you will be equipped with knowledge and abilities for a wide range of careers within the area. From positions like data engineer, software developer and software engineer, you will be able to keep growing in IT indefinitely.\n\nAre you interested in the latest technological developments? Are you curious, a little quirky, and someone who follows through? The Software Engineering course may be what you\'re looking for!</item>

        <item>Do you have a keen eye and ear on the stories behind brands and people? Are you creative with text and image, and fascinated by the world of media? Then the Communication course may be what you\'re looking for!\n\nOrganisations face major challenges. Promoting a new product, working with clients, employees and inhabitants, showing that you\'re doing good things for society. How do you manage, in this time of critical journalism, vlogging, societal discussions and rapidly changing trends?\n\nIn four years, our Communication course will turn you into a, what we proudly call, smart connector. A professional that can create smart connections. Using for example social tools, storytelling, big data and co-creation. You will be developing creative concepts such as media campaigns, events and story platforms. Based on good research, theory and strategy, and of course your own surprising ideas.\n\nFrom year 1 you\'ll be working with clients from the real world. From entrepreneurs from Rotterdam, start-ups and bureaus to national organizations. We work with innovative methods. You\'ll be working with the Scrum method, in which you flexibly and intensively work with the client. No class, course or project is the same. We will change the work type to what you learn: webinars, TED Talks, content cafés, meet-ups, guest lessons and company visits.</item>

        <item>At our school, studying often looks different. As a designer, you will not spend as much time in classrooms in the traditional way. We work together in the studio, for real clients.\n\nYou will design meaningful interactive products and services for the human being: from websites, apps, interactive setups, to full-on experience. Before you start designing, you will do elaborate research into the needs of the users and the environment in which your interactive design will be implemented. You will continuously check in with the client for whom you are designing, and you will also visit them on location. After all, designing is: making prototypes, testing, failing, redesigning, testing, adjusting, et cetera. You\'ll be busy sketching, researching and building on location. You will learn how to work around the needs and experience of the users and the clients. A pro-active attitude is a prerequisite for the designing process in Communication and Multimedia Design, as well as a healthy dose of curiosity, guts, and independence to deliver high quality work. We also expect you to be able to have a critical look at your own work, and act accordingly.\n\nThe first-year students now focus on elderly people that in some way experience physical or mental health problems and need caregiving. The client is seeking smart, new technological applications that will allow elderly people to live at home with the help of caregivers.\n\nThe CMD course challenges you to use your knowledge, creativity and talents for design for interactive products and services, that will improve the lives and environments of the people that use them.</item>

        <item>As a computer engineer, you work on modern IT systems that integrate hardware and software alike. Thanks to your knowledge in programming and hardware, you can work right where they overlap.\n\nIn our everyday lives, we have become increasingly dependent on IT systems. Traveling using public transport is only possible through OV Chipcard, your luggage at Schiphol ends up in the right location automatically, energy gauges become \'smart\' and medical procedures are sometimes performed by devices, and not by a surgeon. These are all examples where hard- and software come together to form a single system.\n\nAs a computer engineer, you will contribute to developing, securing, and maintaning these systems. During the course, you will learn the technical aspects of IT. You will learn to program in various languages, including the so-called \'lower-level\' languages for hardware applications. Using this, you will learn to develop solutions for various devices, robots and other modern systems. You are an all-rounder on all disciplines, but you also specialise in one or more aspects of the workfield. Think for example Machine Learning, Augmented Reality, Automated Systems and, of course, the IoT (Internet of Things), closely tied to Embedded Systems.</item>

    <item>Creative technologists invent and develop innovative digital products, with which the user is the main focus.\n\nAs CMGTer, you are a developer of interactive digital products: you develop web- and mobile apps and you know the basis of game development. The boundaries between these digital products and the physical world continue to fade ever faster. Therefore you will not be educated as a specialist in one specific programming language or platform, but as a flexible programmer that can teach themselves the possibilities of a new language or platform (smartphone, game console, Internet of Things) quickly and efficiently, with the goal of creating and developing interactive solutions for clients, that cross the borders of platforms and programming langages, in mind.\n\nA CMGTer from Rotterdam sets themselves apart from other programmers through sheer creativity, design-focused approach, and the knowledge and sense for the interaction between devices and people. With everything you create, the person you create it for is the focus of your thought process. That is why you will need a researching attitude, and you\'d want to get to know your users and involve them in the creation process of your product as much as possible. The work and possibilities of this creative technologist are heavily subject to change because of the continuous developments in the area. Now, the focus in the course is on web- and mobile technologies. Game technologies form a smaller part.\n\nCMGT-students will work together with students from the Communication and Multimedia Design course at times. This collaboration is important because working together with other creative specialists like designers and strategists when developing interactive solutions, leads to a higher quality end product.\n\nAfter the course, CMGTers will work as programmers at internet bureaus or other bureaus in the creative sector (advertising, marketing, design, innovation). A part will start their own business, or will work as a freelancer. Web Developer and Mobile Developer are also by far the careers that many graduates follow after completing the course.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="studyCourseHeader">
        <item>Software\nEngineering</item>
        <item>Communication</item>
        <item>Communication and\nMultimedia Design</item>
        <item>Computer\nEngineering</item>
        <item>Creative Media and\nGame Technologies</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--ABOUT CMI PAGE-->
    <string name="aboutcmi_location">Wijnhaven 99–103–107</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_phoneNumber">Phone number: 010 – 794 4000</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_email">Email: CMI-Balie@hr.nl</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_website">Url: Hogeschoolrotterdam.nl</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_questionForm">QUESTION FORM</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_textHeader">Hogeschool Rotterdam (CMI)</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_content">
    With its courses in Communication, Informatics, Technical Informatics,
        Creative Media and Game Technologies and Communication and Multimedia Design,
        the Institute for Communication, Media and Information Technology (CMI)
        has no fewer than 3000 students who make a valuable contribution to the
        unlimited world of communication, media and IT.

    </string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_floorplan">FLOORPLAN</string>
    <string name="aboutcmi_courses">COURSES</string>

    <!--FLOORPLAN PAGE-->
    <string name="floorplan_location">Wijnhaven 99-103-107</string>
    <string name="floorplan_floor_header">Floor</string>
    <string name="floorplan_building_header">Building</string>

    <string name="floorplan_up">+</string>
    <string name="floorplan_down">-</string>
    <string name="questionform_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="questionform_subject">Subject:</string>
    <string name="questionform_email">E-mail:</string>
    <string name="questionform_message">Message:</string>
    <string name="questionform_send">SEND</string>
    <string name="cmi_couses">CMI Courses</string>
    <string name="Communicatie">Communicatie</string>
    <string name="Communication_and_Multimedia_Design">Communication and Multimedia Design</string>
    <string name="Creative_Media_and_Game_Technologies">Creative Media and Game Technologies</string>
    <string name="Informatica">Informatica</string>
    <string name="software_engineering">Software Engineering</string>
    <string name="computer_engineering">Computer Engineering</string>

    <!--POPUPS-->
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="classroom">Classroom</string>
    <string-array name="firstTimeArray">
        <item>12:30</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
        <item>12:00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="secondTimeArray">
        <item>14:00</item>
        <item>14:00</item>
        <item>14:45</item>
        <item>14:00</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="thirdTimeArray">
        <item>16:30</item>
        <item>16:45</item>
        <item>16:30</item>
        <item>16:00</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
